{
    "subject": "resource/William_F._Allen_(Delaware)",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Delaware",
    "human_readable": "William F. Allen was born in Delaware.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9052366614341736,
            "question": "Where was William F. Allen born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6414859890937805,
            "question": "What historical events occurred in Delaware during William F. Allen's lifetime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5943431258201599,
            "question": "Who are some other notable people born in Delaware?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3773459494113922,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about William F. Allen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3269295394420624,
            "question": "Is there anything else we know about William F. Allen's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26205703616142273,
            "question": "What state is Delaware known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18130967020988464,
            "question": "What is the history of Delaware as a state?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09768155962228775,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist destinations in Delaware?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.094696544110775,
            "question": "What industries are prominent in Delaware?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07866194099187851,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Delaware?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=William F. Allen was born in Delaware.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3220_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What industries are prominent in Delaware?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3220_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular tourist destinations in Delaware?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3220_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of Delaware as a state?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3220_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3220_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3220_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3220_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3220_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3220_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3220_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3220_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3220_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3220_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3220_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents confirms that William Franklin Allen, also known as William F. Allen, was indeed born in Bridgeville, Delaware, in 1883 (as stated in the document with file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3220/re-ranker-msmarco/78.txt`)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that William Franklin Allen was born in Bridgeville, Delaware, in 1883. Therefore, the statement \"William F. Allen was born in Delaware\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}